signature_latte recipe

Ingredients
1/2 cup milk
1/3 cup freshly brewed coffee or espresso
Drip coffee maker: A basic coffee maker is all you’ll need for this recipe. If you’ve been looking into updating your current one, take your pick of great drip coffee makers from our roundup of favorites.
Small saucepan: A 1 qt. saucepan is a great size for heating up your milk. It’s small and will heat your milk quickly so that your latte will be in your hands as quickly as possible on busy mornings.
Milk frother: A handheld milk frother will take your latte from a basic at-home drink to something out of a coffee shop! This will get your milk to foam up just the way many coffee drinks require.

Directions
Step 1: Make coffee (or espresso)
Step 2: Froth milk
Step 3: Pour milk over espresso

Ready